<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Driving License</string>
    <string name="license_a1">License A1</string>
    <string name="license_a2">License A2</string>
    <string name="text_chose_license_A1">You chose practice license A1</string>
    <string name="text_chose_license_A2">You chose practice license A2</string>
    <string name="text_exam">Driver\'s license test</string>
    <string name="text_learning_theory">Learning theory</string>
    <string name="text_road_signs">Road traffic signs</string>
    <string name="text_tips">Tips for high results</string>
    <string name="text_search_law">Law lookup</string>
    <string name="text_create_random_exam">Create random exam</string>
    <string name="text_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="text_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer">Explain the answer</string>
    <string name="text_question_important">Important question</string>
    <string name="text_60_question_important">60 questions important</string>
    <string name="text_concepts_and_rules">Concepts and rules</string>
    <string name="text_about_83">Includes 83 questions (18 questions important)</string>
    <string name="text_culture_and_ethic">Driving culture and ethics</string>
    <string name="text_about_5">Includes 5 questions</string>
    <string name="text_about_65">Includes 65 questions</string>
    <string name="text_about_35">Includes 35 questions</string>
    <string name="text_driving_technique">Driving technique</string>
    <string name="text_about_12">Includes 12 questions (2 questions important)</string>
    <string name="text_sat_figure">Sat figure</string>
    <string name="text_exam_number">Exam question </string>
    <string name="text_start_exam">Start taking the test</string>
    <string name="text_content_information_A1_license">
        Class A1 driver\'s license exam consists of 25 questions to work on in 19 minutes.\n\nTo pass the test, you need to answer 21/25 questions correctly and not get any wrong points.
    </string>
    <string name="text_content_information_A2_license">
        Class A1 driver\'s license exam consists of 25 questions to work on in 19 minutes.\n\nTo pass the test, you need to answer 21/25 questions correctly and not get any wrong points.
    </string>
    <string name="text_end">End test</string>

    <!-- ======================================== Giải thích đáp án ========================================-->
    <!-- 60 câu điểm liệt-->
    <string name="text_explain_answer_important_1">Obviously answer 3 is wrong. Damage to state property. If you violate, you will be fined with a large amount of money. Specifically:
         \nA fine of between VND 5,000,000 and 10,000,000 for one of the following violations:\n
        a) Illegally drilling, digging, cutting roads and sidewalks;\n
        b) Arbitrarily breaking the median strip, bridge mirror, works, traffic safety equipment on the road;\n
        c) Arbitrarily removing, opening and damaging manhole covers, manhole covers of underground works, tunnel systems on roads;
        d) Illegally blasting or exploiting soil, sand, gravel or stones, affecting road works.
    </string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_important_2">
        Acts of racing motor vehicles and special-use motorcycles that do not meet technical safety and environmental protection standards in road traffic are strictly prohibited.
    </string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_important_3">
       Sentences 1 and 2 are wrong because both are illegal racing acts. Illegal racing is a prohibited act specified in the Road Traffic Law. \nThe correct answer is 3.
    </string>
    <!--83 câu khái niệm và quy tắc-->
    <string name="text_explain_answer_concept_and_rule_1">Sentence 1 is wrong because the curb is understood as the edge on both sides of the road. The roadside has the effect of protecting the road surface, this part of the road is usually for people. Not for traffic.\nQuestion 3 is incorrect because the part of the road for motor vehicles is the part of the road used for road motor vehicles and special-use motorcycles\nQuestion 2 is correct because the driveway is the portion of the roadway used for all vehicular traffic.\nTip: The curb is not intended for vehicular traffic.</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_concept_and_rule_2">A lane is a part of a longitudinally divided portion of the roadway, which is wide enough for a vehicle to run safely. Sentence 2 is correct.</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_concept_and_rule_3">Sentence 1 is incorrect because it is divided vertically but lacks enough width for the car to run safely</string>
    <!--5 câu hỏi Văn hóa và đạo đức lái xe-->
    <string name="text_explain_answer_culture_and_ethic_5">All of the above behaviors show a lack of culture when participating in traffic.\nCorrect answer: 4.</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_culture_and_ethic_1">Tip: Have enough width for the vehicle to run safely.</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_culture_and_ethic_2">Answers 2 and 3 are incorrect because the vehicle must be driven in the correct lane, not in any lane with few vehicles and it is mandatory to wear a helmet when participating in traffic on any route.\nAnswer correct: 1.</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_culture_and_ethic_4">Answer 2 is wrong because the scene must be kept to ensure the best evidence collection process\nCorrect answer: 1</string>
    <string name="text_explain_answer_culture_and_ethic_3">Answers 2 and 3 are wrong because the vehicle must be driven in the correct lane, not in any lane with few vehicles and must stop and park at the specified place, not to facilitate the delivery of passengers and goods. chemistry\nCorrect answer: 1</string>
    <!--======================================== End giải thích đáp án ========================================-->

    <!-- ========================================Câu hỏi điểm liệt (60) ========================================-->
    <string name="question_important_1">Which of the following acts are prohibited?</string>
    <string name="question_important_2">Is the act of racing motor vehicles and special-use motorcycles not up to the standards of technical safety and environmental protection in road traffic?</string>
    <string name="question_important_3">When is the vehicle race only done?</string>
    <string name="question_important_4">Is it prohibited to drive a road vehicle with drugs?</string>
    <string name="question_important_5">After drinking alcohol, is it possible to drive motorcycles, cars, or tractors right after that?</string>
    <string name="question_important_6">Is it prohibited to operate a car, motorcycle, or tractor on the road with alcohol in the blood or breath?</string>
    <string name="question_important_7">Using alcohol while driving, if detected, how to handle?</string>
    <string name="question_important_8">According to the Law on Prevention of Harmful Effects of Alcohol and Beer, which of the following subjects are prohibited from using alcohol while participating in traffic?</string>
    <string name="question_important_9">Is the act of delivering motor vehicles or special-use motorcycles to people who are not eligible to drive vehicles in traffic?</string>
    <string name="question_important_10">Is the act of driving a vehicle exceeding the prescribed speed, entering lanes, or overtaking carelessly?</string>
    <string name="question_important_11">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_12">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_13">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_14">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_15">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_16">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_17">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_18">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_19">Confirm</string>
    <string name="question_important_20">Confirm</string>

    <!-- ========================================Câu trả lời câu hỏi điểm liệt ========================================-->

    <string name="answer_important_1_1">Parking on the street</string>
    <string name="answer_important_1_2">Use the bike on the highway at high speed.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_1_3">Damage (intentionally) target stake, spherical mirror, median line.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_1_4">Use your horn and make a U-turn in a residential area.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_2_1">Not strictly prohibited.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_2_2">Prohibited.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_2_3">Prohibited depending on the route.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_2_4">Prohibited depending on vehicle type</string>
    <string name="answer_important_3_1">Taking place on a street with no passersby.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_3_2">Supported by the people.</string>
    <string name="answer_important_3_3">Licensed by the competent authority.</string>

    <!-- ========================================Câu hỏi khái niệm và quy tắc ========================================-->

    <string name="question_concepts_and_rules_1">What is the portion of the roadway used for vehicular traffic?</string>
    <string name="question_concepts_and_rules_2">What is a lane?</string>
    <string name="question_concepts_and_rules_3">In the concepts below, how is \"separator\" understood correctly?</string>

    <!-- ========================================Câu trả lời khái niệm và quy tắc ========================================-->

    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_1_1">Sidewalks and curbs.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_1_2">Part of the driveway.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_1_3">Motor vehicle section.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_2_1">As part of the longitudinally divided portion of the roadway, used for vehicle traffic.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_2_2">Part of a longitudinally divided portion of the roadway, having a width sufficient for safe driving.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_2_3">As part of a longitudinally divided roadway, there is enough width for cars to run safely.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_3_1">Part of the road to separate vehicles from entering unauthorized places.</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_3_2">Is a part of the road to separate the roadway and traffic safety corridor</string>
    <string name="answer_concepts_and_rules_3_3">Part of a road used to divide the road surface into two separate lanes or to divide the road part of motor vehicles and rudimentary vehicles.</string>
    <!-- ========================================Câu hỏi Văn hóa và đạo đức lái xe ========================================-->

    <string name="question_culture_and_ethics_1">How is the correct concept of traffic culture understood?</string>
    <string name="question_culture_and_ethics_2">In the following behaviors, how should motorists with traffic culture behave?</string>
    <string name="question_culture_and_ethics_3">In the behaviors below, how should a car driver with traffic culture behave?</string>
    <string name="question_culture_and_ethics_4">When a traffic accident occurs and someone is seriously injured, what should the driver and people present at the scene of the accident do?</string>
    <string name="question_culture_and_ethics_5">On the road there is a traffic jam, which of the following behaviors is a lack of culture when participating in traffic?</string>

    <!-- ========================================Câu trả lời Văn hóa và đạo đức lái xe ========================================-->
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_1_1">Being the understanding and strict observance of traffic laws; sense of responsibility to the community when participating in traffic.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_1_2">Is a cultured behavior, with love for people in unfortunate situations when participating in traffic.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_1_3">Both points 1 and 2.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_2_1">Control the vehicle to go on the right in the direction you go; go in the right part of the road and lane; Wear a standard helmet, properly fastened the straps.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_2_2">Driving the vehicle on the part of the road or lane with few vehicles participating in traffic</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_2_3">Wear a helmet where there are signs that require helmets</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_3_1">Control the vehicle to go on the right in the direction you go; go in the right part of the road and lane; stop and park the vehicle at the specified place; If you\'ve been drinking, don\'t drive.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_3_2">Driving the vehicle on the part of the road or lane with little traffic; stopping or parking at a convenient place or at the request of passengers or relatives.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_3_3">Stop and park the vehicle at a convenient place for the delivery of passengers and goods; If you use less alcohol, you can drive.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_4_1">Perform first aid in an emergency; Report the accident to law enforcement.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_4_2">Quickly drive the accident vehicle or hitchhike away from the scene of the accident.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_4_3">Both points 1 and 2.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_5_1">Continuously honk the horn to urge the vehicles ahead to give way.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_5_2">Walk up the sidewalk, make use of every space to quickly get out of the traffic jam.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_5_3">Cross into the left lane and try to overtake another vehicle.</string>
    <string name="answer_culture_and_ethics_5_4">All of the above comments.</string>

</resources>